<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Buy Bitcoin Worldwide</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 23:43:39 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 23:43:39 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Buy an iPhone with Bitcoin</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret: at Buy Bitcoin Worldwide, we’re holders. We value our bitcoins, and don’t go looking to spend them. However, if a merchant offers a large discount for paying with bitcoins then it may be worth it to spend bitcoins instead of fiat currency. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to show you an example of when one might want to spend bitcoins instead of holding them. The iPhone is a commonly used, somewhat expensive device. We’ll use it as an example to show you the kind of discounts that are out there for Bitcoin users. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An iPhone, purchased without a contract, costs hundreds of dollars. By spending bitcoins you can easily save over $100 dollars, or more, if you’re not in a rush and are patient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;purseio&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://buybitcoinww.co/purse_io&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/a&gt; is an escrow service. They match buyers, who want to buy bitcoins, with spenders who are looking to spend bitcoins. Spenders first create an Amazon wish list containing the items they wish to order. The spender then adds the list to &lt;a href=&quot;http://buybitcoinww.co/purse_io&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/a&gt; along with a requested discount. For example if you want to buy $100 worth of items at a 15% discount, you’d offer $85 worth of bitcoins to the buyer who orders your wish list for you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discount comes from buyers who exchange their Amazon credit for bitcoins. Gift card credits are hard to exchange. Buying items on Amazon for someone else is an easy way to get bitcoins in return for the gift card credit that buyers don’t want.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buyers can browse all of the wish lists on &lt;a href=&quot;http://buybitcoinww.co/purse_io&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/a&gt;. Buyers then order the items for spenders. Upon delivery the buyer will receive the agreed upon amount of bitcoins, and the spender receives the items that were on his wish list. It may take a few days  for someone to order your items, especially for a more expensive item like the iPhone. I’ve had luck getting 35% discounts but had to wait almost ten days. A 20% discount should get your items ordered within two days and delivered within a week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of this post, an iPhone 6S 16 GB &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Apple-iPhone-Warranty-Unlocked-Cellphone/dp/B015E8TKS0/ref=sr_1_2?s=wireless&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1446221985&amp;amp;sr=1-2&amp;amp;keywords=iphone+6s&quot;&gt;costs $715&lt;/a&gt; on Amazon. A 20% discount would save you $143 and bring the total price down to $572. Imagine using &lt;a href=&quot;http://buybitcoinww.co/purse_io&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/a&gt; for all of your spending. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re in a rush, &lt;a href=&quot;http://buybitcoinww.co/purse_io&quot;&gt;Purse.io&lt;/a&gt; offers an instant service: Purse Instant. You save 5% and your item is delivered with Amazon prime meaning it gets delivered in 2 days. A 5% discount on a $715 iPhone is still $35.75 of savings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;gyft&quot;&gt;Gyft&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy an iPhone in person, or prefer to buy from somewhere other than Amazon, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gyft.com/&quot;&gt;Gyft&lt;/a&gt; is a good option. Gyft is a digital gift card reseller that gives you 3% back on each purchase made with Bitcoin. The 3% is given to you in the form of Gyft Points. Your Gyft points can be saved and put towards future purchases like an iPhone. To buy the iPhone with Gyft you can buy a gift card for use at eBay, Target, Amazon, or Best Buy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that Bitcoin offers some amazing opportunities for discounts and arbitrage. Be sure to take advantage of it whenever possible. Remember, your bitcoins are valuable and better than fiat money. Merchants should have to offer you a discount in order to get you to spend your bitcoins. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/kb/which-countries-mine-export-most-bitcoins/&quot;&gt;Which countries mine the most bitcoins?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/buy-an-iphone-with-bitcoin/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/buy-an-iphone-with-bitcoin/</guid>
        
        
        <category>shopping</category>
        
        <category>saving</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Common and Costly Bitcoin Mistakes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin can be hard to understand, and, therefore, difficult to use. It takes a bit of effort to spend or secure bitcoins. We want to help you avoid rookie mistakes that we’ve seen countless times. If you follow the principles laid out in this list, you’ll prevent yourself from silly errors that will cost you both money and time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bitcoin-payments-are-irreversible&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Payments are Irreversible&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin payments are irreversible. If you send bitcoins to the wrong address, there is a very small chance you’ll get them back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t understand how to send and receive bitcoins, learn more before trying with larger amounts. Buy a small amount; like $5 worth. Send a few small payments back and forth between wallets to get a feel for how Bitcoin payments work. Don’t deal with larger amounts of bitcoin until you’re comfortable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;leaving-bitcoins-on-an-exchange&quot;&gt;Leaving Bitcoins on an Exchange&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Those who do not learn history are doomed to repeat it. - George Santayana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take these words of wisdom and learn about the history of Bitcoin scams. Bitcoin exchanges play a crucial role in Bitcoin’s economy. People need an easy way to exchange their fiat currency for bitcoins. But, do not use Bitcoin exchanges as a wallet or store coins on an exchange for an extended period of time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are countless cases of people leaving bitcoins on an exchange, only to have the exchange shut down and run away with all of the bitcoins. The most famous example of this is Mt. Gox. Over 650,000 bitcoins were lost when Mt. Gox shut down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never store bitcoins on an exchange or with a third party. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;storing-large-amounts-of-bitcoin-in-a-hot-wallet&quot;&gt;Storing Large amounts of Bitcoin in a Hot Wallet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoins are valuable, and scammers frequently target Bitcoin users. If you have a significant amount of bitcoins, make sure that your coins are secured properly. Use hardware wallets and cold storage to be certain that hackers cannot take your coins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardware wallets like the Ledger Nano and TREZOR are simple solutions that will protect your bitcoins. Paper wallets are another option.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dont-ever-delete-a-bitcoin-wallet&quot;&gt;Don’t Ever Delete a Bitcoin Wallet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sigh… why delete a wallet instead of moving it aside and keeping the old copy just in case? You should never delete a wallet. – Satoshi Nakamoto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Satsohi Nakamoto, Bitcoin’s creator, told people to never delete a wallet. Bitcoin addresses can only be generated one time. If you create a wallet and lose the wallets private keys, any bitcoins stored in that wallet are gone forever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to Satoshi. Don’t end up like James Howells, the British man who trashed a hard drive that contained his Bitcoin wallet with over 7,500 bitcoins (about $2.5 million dollars at the time of this post).  Unfortunately, James’ bitcoins are gone forever as the hard drive is likely destroyed or ruined even it were to be found. Learn from James and don’t delete a wallet no matter how much money you’re dealing with. You never know. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/kb/which-countries-mine-export-most-bitcoins/&quot;&gt;Which countries mine the most bitcoins?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/common-costly-bitcoin-mistakes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/common-costly-bitcoin-mistakes/</guid>
        
        
        <category>mining</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 10 Biggest Bitcoin Mining Pools and Companies</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin miners are crucial to Bitcoin and its security. Without miners, Bitcoin would be vulnerable and easy to attack. Most Bitcoin users don’t mine. However, miners are responsible for the creation of all new bitcoins and a fascinating part of the Bitcoin ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mining, once done on the average home computer, is now mostly done in large, specialized warehouses. These warehouses usually direct their hashing power towards mining pools. What is a mining pool? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitcoinmining.com/bitcoin-mining-pools/&quot;&gt;BitcoinMining.com&lt;/a&gt; breaks it down: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin mining pools are a way for Bitcoin miners to pool their resources together and share their hashing power while splitting the reward equally according to the amount of shares they contributed to solving a block.
&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;A &quot;share&quot; is awarded to members of the Bitcoin mining pool who present a valid proof of work that their Bitcoin miner solved. Bitcoin mining in pools began when the difficulty for mining increased to the point where it could take years for slower miners to generate a block. &lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;The solution to this problem was for miners to pool their resources so they could generate blocks quicker and therefore receive a portion of the Bitcoin block reward on a consistent basis, rather than randomly once every few years. &lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we can see which mining pools are the largest, it’s important to understand that the hash power pointed towards a mining pool isn’t necessarily owned by the mining pool itself. There are a few cases, like with BitFury and KnCMiner, where the company itself runs the mining operation but doesn’t run a mining pool. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin miners can switch mining pools easily by routing their hash power to a different pool. The market share of pools is constantly changing. To make the list of top 10 miners, we looked at blocks found over the past 6 months using data from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blocktrail.com/BTC/pools&quot;&gt;BlockTrail&lt;/a&gt;. The size of mining pools is constantly changing. We will do our best to keep this posted up-to-date. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;discusfishf2poolhttpswwwf2poolcom&quot;&gt;1. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.f2pool.com/&quot;&gt;DiscusFish/F2Pool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DiscusFish, also known as F2Pool, is based in China. DiscusFish has mined about 19.5% of all blocks over the past six months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;antpoolhttpsantpoolcomhomehtm&quot;&gt;2. &lt;a href=&quot;https://antpool.com/home.htm&quot;&gt;AntPool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antpool is another Chinese based mining pool, maintained by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitmaintech.com/about.htm&quot;&gt;BitMain&lt;/a&gt;. Antpool mines about 18.5% of all blocks.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bitfuryhttpwwwbitfuryorg&quot;&gt;3. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bitfury.org/&quot;&gt;BitFury&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BitFury is one of the largest producers of Bitcoin mining hardware and chips. BitFury currently mines about 13% of all bitcoins in three data centers across Georgia. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;btcchttpspoolbtcchinacom&quot;&gt;4. &lt;a href=&quot;https://pool.btcchina.com/&quot;&gt;BTCC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BTCC is China’s third largest Bitcoin exchange. Its mining pool currently mines about 11.5% of all blocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bw-poolhttpswwwbwcom&quot;&gt;5. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bw.com/&quot;&gt;BW Pool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BW, established in 2014, is another mining company based in China. It currently mines about 8% of all blocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kncminerhttpwwwkncminercom&quot;&gt;6. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kncminer.com/&quot;&gt;KnCMiner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sweden is home to KnCMiner, a Bitcoin mining manufacturer based in Stockholm. KnCMiner currently mines about 6% of all blocks. KnCMiner is not a pool and mines bitcoins in their own warehouses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;slushhttpsminingbitcoinczhome&quot;&gt;7. &lt;a href=&quot;https://mining.bitcoin.cz/home/&quot;&gt;Slush&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slush was the first mining pool and currently mines about 5% of all blocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inchttps21co&quot;&gt;8. &lt;a href=&quot;https://21.co/&quot;&gt;21 Inc.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21 Inc. is a Bitcoin mining company based in California. 21 runs a large amount of miners, but also sells low powered bitcoin miners as part of their 21 Bitcoin computer. Most of the hash power from the 21 Bitcoin computers is pointed towards 21’s mining pool. 21 Inc. mines about 4% of all bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eligiushttpeligiusstgateway&quot;&gt;9. &lt;a href=&quot;http://eligius.st/~gateway/&quot;&gt;Eligius&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eligius was one of the first mining pools created. It currently mines about 3% of all blocks. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ghashiohttpsghashio&quot;&gt;10.	&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghash.io/&quot;&gt;GHASH.IO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GHASH.IO used to be the largest mining pool, with over 50% of the network. However, concerns over a 51% attack caused many miners to transfer their hash power to other pools. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/kb/which-countries-mine-export-most-bitcoins/&quot;&gt;Which countries mine the most bitcoins?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/biggest-bitcoin-mining-pools/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.buybitcoinworldwide.com/blog/biggest-bitcoin-mining-pools/</guid>
        
        
        <category>mining</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
